蛇蝎美人
第一季 第十二集
幻象 上集
Visions Part 1
早上好 Cuesta Verde
Good morning, Cuesta Verde.
希望你有个美妙的清晨
Hope you're having a wonderful morning.
如果你在期盼一个美妙的夜晚
And if you're looking forward to a wonderful evening,
你可能想咨询一下Foster Prentiss
you might want to check out Foster Prentiss,
他是一个通灵人 他不可思议
the psychic who has spellbound audiences
的通灵术让观众痴迷
with his incredible medium skills.
如果你是第4个打进电话来的人
And if you're the fourth caller,
你会获得两张已经售罄的
you'll get two tickets
今晚在奥秘庄园
to tonight's sold-out show at the Mysterium Manor
的两个小时娱乐表演的门票
for two hours of entertainment
那一定会让你从怀疑
that's sure to turn even you skeptics
转变为彻底的信服
into true believers.
15分钟后 我们会让Prentiss
And in 15 minutes, we'll have Prentiss,
在播音室现场直播
live on air in our studio,
但是首先我们要向Colleen Gray了解一下交通情况
but first we're gonna go Colleen Gray with traffic.
Colleen 那里情况怎么样
Colleen, how's it look out there?
好的
Here you go.
现在 女士们先生们
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
Foster Prentiss 神奇奥秘
Foster Prentiss, the Amazing Mysterium.
好啊
Bravo!
晚上好 欢迎各位
Good evening and welcome.
今晚 你们都是被
You've all been invited here
特别邀请来到这里
today by special invitation
见证只有极少数
to witness something very few
人才能体验的事情
people get to experience.
我们将一同伸出我们的手
Together, we're going to reach out
穿越我们所知的世界
past the world as we know it
触摸未知的时空
and touch beyond.
也许 仅仅是也许 如果我们非常幸运
And then maybe, just maybe, if we're very lucky,
我们会了解到未来
we'll learn something about the beyond
和我们自己的事情
and also about ourselves.
啊 谢谢光临
Ah. Thanks for coming.
介意告诉我你的大名吗 先生
Do you mind telling me your name, sir?
你是神奇奥秘 你应该知道
You're the Amazing Mysterium. You tell me.
好 我会的
Okay. I shall.
哦 你是Richard Hollis
Oh, it's "Richard Hollis.
你住在604 Kirkside Drive, Cuesta Verde, California
"604 Kirkside Drive, Cuesta Verde, California.
1970年
1970"--
我年你更像是69年生人 你认为如何
More like a '69 baby to me, don't you think?
你真应该注意一下
You should really keep an eye
你的财产 Hollis先生
on your belongings, Mr. Hollis.
我能提个问题吗
Can I ask you a question?
你相认我们能看到
Do you believe that we can see
你所知道的世界的未来吗
beyond the world as you know it?
我相信你做的就是在瞎扯蛋
I believe what you do is a load of crap.
恕我冒昧 先生
No disrespect, sir,
但是我的朋友非要拉我来看你表演
but my friend here dragged me to your show.
没关系 没关系 我完全理解
Please, please. I totally understand.
你瞧 我过去和你一样 Hollis先生
You see, I used to be very much like you, Mr. Hollis.
直到我开始有了幻觉
That was until I started having the visions.
你能让我摸一下你的手吗
Would you be so kind to let me touch your hand?
但是我们才刚见面
But we've only just met.
拜托了
Please.
哦 你正在想你的父亲
Oh, you're thinking about your father.
他的名字是Ike 不 不不 等等 叫Mike
His name is Ike. No, no, no. Wait. Mike.
Michael Samuel Hollis
Michael Samuel Hollis.
我说的对吗
Is that right?
哦 非常接近
Oh, you were very close.
他教过你怎么滑冰 在缅因州的一个
He taught you how to ice skate on a
池塘上 你在那里长大
pond in Maine where you grew up.
大约一年 一年前
About a year-- year ago,
他得了病 病得很重
he got sick, very sick,
他去世了
and he died.
嗯 他去世那天是Richard的生日 3月7日
Mmm, died on Richard's birthday, March 7.
他是在你的生日那天 3月7日去世的
He died on your birthday, March 7.
- 你怎么知道的 - 因为他就在这里 Hollis先生
- How do you know that? - Cause he's here, Mr. Hollis.
我们说话的时候他的灵魂就在这个屋子里
His spirit is in the room as we speak.
他是个Cuesta Verde大学的历史教授
He's a history professor at Cuesta Verde University.
废柴啊
What a loser.
你是个历史学教授
You're a history professor.
为什么你不告诉他他爱他
Why don't you tell him he loves him?
要知道他们都爱听到这个
You know they always love to hear that.
他想让你知道
He wants you to know
他是那么地爱你
he loves you very much
而且永远爱着你
and always will.
The Amazing Mysterium.
好啊
Bravo!
你可真是个浪货 我告诉你
You're a hot piece of crumpet, I tell you.
英语口音已经说够了
Enough with the English accent already.
拜托 你说这能让你兴奋
Come on. You said it turns you on.
是你让我兴奋
You turn me on.
额的神 你还真是欲求不满啊
Jesus, you're insatiable.
神奇奥秘可不是白叫的
They don't call me the Amazing Mysterium for nothing.
别吹牛了
Don't flatter yourself.
哦 上帝 你真是个贱货
Aw, Jesus, you're such a cunt.
你非要扫我的兴 是吗
You have to ruin it, don't you?
你知道我正在经历一段艰难时期
You know I'm going through a rough patch.
更像一个没钱的时期
More like a broke patch.
是啊 很不幸 我伟大的幻境
Yeah, unfortunately, my greatest illusion
使得所有人都认为我很有钱
is making everybody think that I'm rich.
你知道吗 那不是我的问题
You know what? That's not my problem.
我需要更多的钱
I need more money.
我也有开销啊 你知道
I have expenses, too, you know.
你得到了门票收入的2.5%
You get two and a half percent of the gate,
加上这个活的所有其他额外收入
plus all the other perks of doing this job.
我想现在已经够多的了
I think that's enough for now.
如果你把和你上床也当作额外收入 再考虑一下
If you consider fucking you a perk, think again.
哦 拜托 说好听点儿 你就是个电话接线员
Oh, come on. You're a glorified phone operator.
什么 你不就是挤了挤乳沟 露了点大腿吗
What, you show a little bit of cleavage, some leg?
谁都能干你的活
Anybody can do your job.
我认为你那份已经足够了 好吧
I think your cut is quite enough, all right?
你给我听着 如果这事还是没有转机
You know what? If things don't change around here,
我就把真相告诉所有人
I'm gonna tell everybody the truth
关于你这个不神奇奥秘的一切
about the not-so-amazing Mysterium.
把你的魔术棒从我面前拿开 不然我就给TMZ打电话
Get your magic wand out of my face or I'm calling TMZ.
注：TMZ 全称Thirty Mile Zone 一个专门搜集名人的八卦和花边的网站
你想毁了我吗 你不能
You're gonna ruin me? You can't.
我欠一屁股债 我需要那些钱
I'm in debt, and I need that money.
你知道这里的房租
Do you realize how much the rent
和日常开销有多少吗
and the overhead is on this place?
我明白最近的生意
I understand that things have
变得有点萧条
been a little bit slow recently,
而观众们不会像过去那样好忽悠了
but they don't just make suckers like they used to.
好吧 那些不是我的问题
Well, that's not my problem.
拜托 你得再给我点时间
Come on. You've got to give me a little bit more time,
那样我们才能重新谈
then we can renegotiate.
时间到了
Time's up.
你知道 那不是个好态度 Tara
You know, that's not a very healthy attitude, Tara.
我对你的把戏感到恶心
I am so sick of your tricks.
别他妈威胁我
Don't you threaten me.
这不是恶作剧
This is not a trick.
我会让你永远消失
I'm gonna make you disappear forever.
读心术是一种表演艺术
Mentalism is a performing art
那些从业者能够表现出
whose practitioners demonstrate
高度发达的精神力和准确的直觉
highly developed mental and intuitive abilities
比如说传心术 千里眼 心灵控制
such as telepathy, clairvoyance, and mind control.
Foster Prentiss 神奇奥秘
Foster Prentiss, the Amazing Mysterium,
压根儿就没这种能力
possesses no such skill.
他是个彻头彻尾的骗子
He is a complete and utter fraud.
不幸的是 压根就没有假的谋杀案这么一说
Unfortunately, there's nothing phony about murder.
Foster会不惜一切代价得到他想要的东西
Foster will stop at nothing to get what he wants
并将表演人生中最重要的一场演出
and must put on a performance of a lifetime.
也许这次
But maybe this time,
他会被人算计
the ruse is on him.
有什么需要吗
Can I help you?
我想我们能互相帮助
I think we can help each other.
听说你们在找一个新的助手
I hear you're looking for a new assistant.
我看了你得表演 你棒极了
I've seen your act. You're very good.
但如果你得到合理的帮助的话 你会变得很伟大
But you could be great with the right help.
额 我不需要任何帮助 谢谢
Yeah, I'm not looking for any help, thank you.
我穿渔网袜很好看
I look fabulous in fishnets
但不穿更漂亮
and even better without them.
你难道不考虑下让我试镜
Won't you consider letting me audition,
或者至少递给我那条浴巾
or at least fetching me that towel?
顺便说一下 我叫Jessica
By the way, my name is Jessica.
很高兴见到你 Jessica
Pleased to meet you, Jessica.
这真是个给力的面试啊
That was a very convincing job interview.
你的推荐信无可挑剔
Your references are impeccable.
两者都很完美
Both of them.
好了 我压根儿就不需要有幻觉
Well, I don't have to have visions
就知道你注定会有所成就 Prentiss
to know you're destined for great things, Prentiss.
我只想做那伟大成功中的一小部分
I just want to be a small part of that success.
多小
How small?
我不想成为那个杀了下金蛋的鹅的人
I don't want to be the one to kill the golden goose.
我认为那足以满足每个人的要求
I think there's enough to go around for everyone.
你确定
You sure about that?
你读我的想法吧
Read my mind.
唉 我认为那不是你的想法
Yeah, I don't think that's your mind.
我知道如何得到
I know how to score
一大笔现金
some serious cash,
但是我需要你的帮助
but I need you help.
我被介绍认识了一个有钱的老女人
I was introduced to a rich old lady.
她女儿失踪了
Her daughter went missing.
她猜想可能死了
Thinks she might be dead.
她想和她女儿谈话
She wants to communicate with
在另一个世界交流下
her from beyond the grave.
你觉得你能为她们联络上吗
Think you can connect them?
恩 我想我可以
Yeah, I think I can do that.
你要做的就是让那老女人确信
All you gotta do is convince her
你可以和另一个世界交流
you can communicate with the afterworld,
只要给她们个交流的机会
set up a private reading,
她就会付钱
and she'll pay...
好吧
big time.
这很有意思
It's very interesting.
你跟你简历里的照片一点儿都不一样
You don't look anything like your profile picture.
你真的是个医生吗
Are you really a doctor?
不是
No.
你真的是个鬼神学家吗
Are you really a demonologist?
是的
Yes.
好给力
Cool.
那些神奇奥秘到底要做些什么
And how can the Amazing Mysterium
才会让你吃惊呢 亲爱的
amaze and astound you, my dear?
请告诉我你得名字
Please tell me your name.
Veronica Lombard
Veronica Lombard.
Veronica Lombard,
我将会告诉你一些你关于你自己的
I'm gonna tell you something about yourself
别人都不知道的事
that nobody else knows.
靠
Shit!
Foster 我们有麻烦了
Foster, we got a problem.
能听见我说话吗 Foster
can you hear me? Foster!
Veronica Lombard
Veronica Lombard...
抱歉 我觉得我好像
I'm sorry. I feel like I'm being
被那双美丽的眼睛分散了注意力
distracted by those lovely eyes.
额 给我点时间集中精力
Um, just give me a second to compose myself again.
哇 我从来没有过
Wow, I've never had this kind of
读心如此困难的状况
trouble getting a reading before.
你有一个神奇的
You have this amazing,
特别的气场在你周围
very special aura around you.
我预言你的将来
I predict great happiness
会得到巨大的幸福和成功
and success in your future.
哇 真幸运啊
Um, good luck. Yeah.
结婚纪念日快乐
Happy anniversary.
Greg
Greg?
回答我
Answer me!
等我办完出院手续后 我要去玩些狂野刺激的
When I check out, I'm gonna go out something fierce.
别啊
Please don't--
清场 啊
Clear! Aah!
你是一名护士
You're a nurse.
是的，我曾是
Yes, I was.
你在医院工作
You worked at a hospital.
我换工作了 工作不顺心
I made a career change. Didn't really work out.
在医院里发生了一些事情
Something happened at the hospital.
还记得你跟我说
Remember when you told me
你想要做一些疯狂的事情吗
that you wanted to go out something fierce?
好的 猜猜看 我将会满足你的愿望
Well, guess what? You're gonna get your wish.
啊  天哪
Oh, my.
你看到了什么
What did you see?
失配一下 女士们先生们
Excuse me, ladies and gentlemen.
中场休息
It's-- It's time for the intermission.
我不知道我是怎么办到的
I don't know how this can beappening to me.
我看到了她的过去 我看到她以前干过的事情
I saw her, I saw what she did,
而且我看到她杀了一个男人
and I saw her kill a guy.
她肯定知道了我知道了这一切
She knows that I know.
她肯定知道了
She knows I know.
我该怎么办 我现在该怎么办呢
What am I gonna do? What am I gonna do now?
你只需要告诉我
You just tell me what--
混蛋
Fucking hell!
你打我了 Jesus 你疯了吗
You hit me? Jesus! You crazy?
冷静下来
Calm the fuck down.
没有人杀人了
Nobody killed anybody.
你什么都没有看见
You didn't see anything.
那简直是天方夜谈
That was incredible.
不管怎样 你的骗局起作用了
Whatever hell scam you're pulling is working.
你看见外面那些人脸上的表情么
Did you see their faces out there?
他们开始相信了
They're eating it up.
是的 不 不  这不是骗局
Yeah-- No, no, it wasn't a scam.
我感觉到的事是真实的
What I felt out there was real.
当然是真的
Sure it was.
但现在 你需要把精力放在工作上
But now...you gotta keep your eye on the prize.
如果我们想要敲那富太太一笔的话
If we're gonna score any of that rich bitch's cash,
她需要被确保
she needs to be believe
你能够跟她死去的女儿交谈
that you can talk to her dead daughter.
所以出去完成这该死的表演
So get out there and finish the show.
好的 好的
Okay, okay.
恩 好的
Yeah, okay.
很好 你已经很好的恢复过来 女士
Well, you've certainly recovered splendidly, ladies,
自从你春天去
from your spring break trip to...
San Padre 我相信
San Padre, I believe.
不 你真不应该
No, you really shouldn't have got
把那下流的纹身纹在你的
that nasty tattoo down on your...
我不会对任何人说的
I'm not gonna say in front of everybody.
并且 不 不要告诉你的父亲
And, no, do not tell your father.
晚上好
Good evening.
我懂了 沉默以对
I get it. The silent treatment.
因为你不相信
Is that because you don't believe,
亦或者怕被人知道你做过的事情吗
or is that because you do?
没关系的 你不需要告诉我什么
It's okay. You don't have to talk.
我很健谈的
I'm very gregarious.
Hey 我是Jay Roma  这里是Crazy Chixx
Hey, this is Jay Roma, Crazy Chixx.
你多大了
How old are you?
刚满18岁
I just turned 18.
做什么工作的
What are you doing?
你说过你想这么做 不是吗
You said you wanted to do this, right?
耶  不 我没有
Yeah-- No, I do.
你灌醉我了
You got me drunk.
随后你毁了我们的人生
And then you ruined our lives.
我们不得不从学校退学 改名字
We had to drop out of school, change our names,
不管我们搬到哪里做过什么
and no matter where we moved or what we did,
我们不能摆脱我们因为你做过的事情
we could not get away from what we did for you!
我们全被你录像了
We all appeared in your videos.
现在该轮到你被我们录像了
Now it's your turn to be in ours.
你们想要干什么
What are you doing?
嗨 嗨   回来  不 回来
Hey-- Hey, come back here. No! Come back!
回来
Come back!
所以你看到的那个男人是Jay Roma
So the man you apparently saw is Jay Roma.
他创办了Crazy Chixx
He started Crazy Chixx.
几个月前他被谋杀了
He was murdered a few months back,
他死亡的视频流传到网上了
and his death was streamed on the Internet.
为什么这会发生在我身上
Why is this happening to me, though?
这是我无法理解的
That's what I don't understand.
另外那妞是Violet Macready
The other tart is Violet Macready.
她对最近两起谋杀案的焦点人物
She is a person of interest in two recent killings:
一件是本地有名望的外科医生
one of a local, prestigious surgeon,
另外一件是某位帮派份子
the other-- some two-bit gangbanger.
你知道的 我从未想过这会是真的
You know, I never thought this was possible.
为什么我被赋予这种超能力呢
Why have I been given such a powerful gift?
你需要考虑的问题是
The question you should be asking yourself
我们如何利用它
is, how can we exploit it?
利用它吗
Exploit it?
天哪 我难道非要一字一句跟你解释明白吗
Jesus! Do I have to spell everything out to you?
勒索
Blackmail.
你已经是一个骗子了
You're already a fraud.
再加一条罪孽又怎么了
What's another sin,
或者再多点
or three?
你不相信我 是吗
You don't believe me, do you?
你看到了一些有趣的事情了吗 大师
Do you see anything interesting, swami?
Logan
Logan.
我原本以为你爱我的
I thought you loved me.
不
No.
从未
Never.
但我要告诉你
But I will say this for you--
你有一个非常不错的心脏
you have a very good heart.
你杀了你男朋友
You killed your boyfriend,
设计陷害了他 并把他的器官卖了
set him up and sold his organs for spare parts.
你怎么能
How did you...
没人知道这些的
No one knows about that.
我告诉你 幻觉是真实的 Jessica
I told you, the visions are real, Jessica.
你知道不 Foster吗
You know what, Foster?
我认为我们将会真的真的很有钱
I think we're gonna be really, really rich.